pixigames.com 2008-04-21

# PixiGames - Privacy Statement

| 

**Privacy Statement for PixiGames**

> **PixiGames** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site:  **PixiGames** 
> 
> ####  Advertisers 
> 
> We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. 
> 
> This site uses the services of UGP Networks, and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 
> 
>   
>  **Third Party Cookies**  
>  In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie?on your browser.  
>    
> 
> 
> ####  Registration Forms 
> 
> Our site's newsletter registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal address), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). 
> 
> Contact information from the registration forms is used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. 
> 
> Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.   
>  This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 
> 
> ####  External Links 
> 
> This site contains links to other sites. **PixiGames** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 
> 
> ####  Public Forums 
> 
> This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 
> 
> ####  Security 
> 
> This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.
> 
> ####  Choice/Opt-Out 
> 
> Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from our partners, and us . 
> 
>   * You can send email to:  [**webmaster@pixigames.com** ](mailto:webmaster@pixigames.com)
> 

> 
> #### Data Quality/Access 
> 
> This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: 
> 
>   * You can send email to:  [**webmaster@pixigames.com** ](mailto:webmaster@pixigames.com)
> 

> 
> ## Contacting the Web Site 
> 
> If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: **  **[**webmaster@pixigames.com**](mailto:webmaster@pixigames.com)

|
